Minna Tankentai
Everybody Explore
Yes, sir.
Next, cut.
Okay, this is Kid Shinji.
Nice to meet you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
We are all explorers.
It's now just after 11:50 on December 31st, and this is a video of us celebrating the year 2023 together.
We're going to welcome the year 2023 together, and we're going to show you the uncensored version of this video.
The current edge will be used as well.
Please be careful. We're going to celebrate the year with the people who are watching with us.
Thank you very much for coming from Budokan.
Now, this is the last video of this year's Expedition.
This is the last video of this year's expedition, and I'd like to take a look back at the 26 videos of this year's Inari Expedition.
Including this video, we have released 26 videos, and guess who has appeared in the most videos?
It's my physical condition, you know.
Oh, I see.
It's your physical condition?
Oh, sure.
What are you watching? Now.
This hatzuri.
You're looking at this and you're choosing it? I'm looking at a person right now.
Oh, I see.
Two of them.
I'd like to announce the most appearances.
And the other two...
We also have the number of appearances.
The most appearances by the Iginari Expedition this year is...
Out of 26 appearances
10 out of 26 appearances this year.
Mr. Yasumoriwaka!
Yay!
Is that him?
Yes, she's here.
Ten times.
Ten times, Mr. Yasumori.
So, I got two of them.
Mr. Miu...
Second place, 9 times.
By the way, how are we doing?
How are we doing?
Not too many.
Not much.
It's been happening a lot lately.
By the way, Shinju-san...
In fiscal year 2021...
Zero times.
Hey, why is that?
Yo, I'd like to hear it from here.
Answer? Answer?
I was thinking...
Shinju-san
In the year 2022.
Third place.
No way!
Feng Shui for lost love
Cheese in moon shape
Mr. Cheese, we've had seven entries.
Thank you very much.
And there are many pairs with Hikarin, aren't there?
Yes, yes, yes...
Eating something...
That's right.
By the way...
We're kind of tied.
Fifth place.
Fifth place, and she's got six.
That's a lot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like I said.
You remember that one we did together?
Do you remember the one we did together, Mr. Moritatsu?
The one with Mr. Moritatsu... the one with the big food video and the announcements.
What a surprise! The video of Moritatsu-san!
This year's Inari Expedition
It's the most viewed video of this year's Inari Expedition.
LOL!
He doesn't eat at all!
The gluttony video!
Really?
Of all the Inari Expedition videos.
of all the Inari Expedition videos.
That makes me happy.
You're happy?
By all means. 23.
I wonder if it's going to grow in size.
Maybe next year we'll have a little revenge.
I'd love to.
Really, 23?
Hey, girl.
We've been eating a lot of each other's food.
That's right.
Didn't you hear? That day
I didn't hear that we were going to shoot a video with Morita san
So you ate by mistake?
I don't know...
It's a secret!
I heard about it, but...
I thought we'd just announce the rankings
Oh...Uh-oh.
The captain told me you usually eat it.
They use this one too.
I thought it was a video about how amazing the forest is without eating.
But then he said, "Normally, you'd eat it.
I think the captain should have done that.
That's what happened... a little bit.
Still, I think Hikaru did his best to eat.
I don't...
How can you say that?
I forgot I hadn't lost any.
Itadakimasu tokadakimasu (Thank you for the food) and takasato (Thank you for the food) were the same amount.
I was just...
I was just pecking away.
That's not good.
That's funny.
So, you two have any other memorable moments?
They were all memorable.
Among them...
Kai-chan's crepe making
was the most memorable one.
That's for sure.
of the legend of Shinchi crepe.
Yes.
I was allowed to make a crepe called Shinchi Crepe
It was delicious!
Crunchy Shinchi crepes.
Crunchy on the outside with a thin crust on the inside.
That was difficult.
Do you remember any of them, Hikaru?
The one I enjoyed the most was...
Infinite Gacha.
You know, the kind where you have to do a lot of rattling?
Rumble Rumble.
You like rattles, right?
I've always loved messing around.
It was a dream come true for me.
We can do that again.
Let's do idols again, too.
That's what I'm talking about.
What kind of year was it for you personally?
The year 2022...
But compared to other years...
I've been on a national tour.
It was probably a year
It was a year
I was allowed to go to many places
How did you relax when you were tired?
how did you heal yourself? I heal myself.
I never get tired.
What?
I have a very healthy body.
I don't catch colds or anything.
You're strong.
I'm really strong.
I'm not like that.
Why are you stroking your belly right now?
I'm kind of bored.
Why?
She's talking. She's not.
How was your day, Karu?
I went to physical therapy.
Therapy? Oh, you mean when you're tired?
I was wondering if you were going to tell me how this year went at all.
A lot has happened this year.
But, I mean...
A lot of things happened.
But I think I was able to look forward and do my best, no matter what happened.
That's great!
Positive!
You managed to live to this day without answering me!
So much! But that's a good thing!
Positive 1022!
Well, that's what the year was like!
How would you describe the year in one common kanji character?
I have a whiteboard here, can you quickly write it down?
By the way, there is only 1 minute and 30 seconds left until the new year!
What?
Kanji characters for this year?
I've got one where the priest writes it with a good pen.
That's crazy! Really? It has a meaning, doesn't it?
Yes, it does!
It's not a clock, is it?
It's not a clock.
No, it's not a clock.
What's the difference?
Can Pearl give us a little explanation?
I am a Han of Han Dynasty.
Why, I am Han Jie Han.
I was in my last year of my teens.
So, I have completed the teenage version of Pearl, which is common in comic books.
I see.
So, in that sense, I am Han, Han of blood.
The second chapter will begin.
The second chapter of Pearl. I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I am.
While I'm at it, let me introduce Hikaru-san's new year's gift.
Eeeee!
I'm going to open it already!
What are you going to do? What are you going to do?What do we do? What do we do?
We only have 20 seconds left!
How do we open it?
Yes, sir.
What do we do now?
Already 15 seconds left.
Thank you all for another year.
See you next year.
Please give my best to Nankanren University.
Let's countdown!
Five.
Three. Two.
Two.
Congratulations!
What's this?
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year to you
It's the year 2023
It's a new year!
It's a new year
It's difficult
Playing live on air
It's the new day.
It's a new day.
Let me show you Hikaru's unfinished business from last year.
Let me introduce one of Hikaru's letters.
I've been...
Potato chips and cup noodles.
I love them!
I like to eat them while I'm slumped over a yogi stick.
I used to love to eat them.
Yes, I did.
About halfway through, I thought I had to warm up a little bit.
I had to change my mindset.
A little bit higher consciousness.
I started to eat a lot of vegetables.
I'm warming up that consciousness.
I told them I was going to put chocolate candy in it, but they said they didn't want it.
What!
So, ha! Consciousness...
Did he hate me? Like that.
No, they didn't hate me at all.
I took what I could get.
I see.
So you have learned to have the courage to say no.
The courage to say "Noh.
You became a Japanese who can say "Noh.
That's right.
Isn't that wonderful?
That was in the year 2000.
Well, it is now the year 2023, so I would like to start off by asking you to write down your goals for this year.
Shall we start with Ms. Pearl? How are you doing? How is your skill?
What's with that smile?
I was in the art club, so I don't know how to use my arms.
You weren't in the sewing club, were you?
I was in the sewing club and then the art club.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Vertical?
Vertical? Vertical? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's how you do a scroll, right?
The way you draw the scrolls, right?
What? Did I get it wrong, Makoto?
Don't you know? You've never done it before? Maybe...
You have, right? We do it at school, you know.
Yes, we do.
What? Vertical, right?
Do you want to check it?
Don't you know where the quarter dimension is?
The quarter inch?
Can I start now?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Here we go.
That's your goal for this year.
Here we go!
Wow, I miss this feeling.
Oh, you're strong.
But you're good, Jane.
You're good.
Oh?
You're right.
They're all on the side.
Oh, man.
Kaki-jun...
Wait a minute.
I have a bad feeling about this.
This year?
I'm not that versatile.
That's the word.
Hey.
I use it all the time.
It's not that versatile.
Is that the right kanji?Is that the right kanji?
Hmm?
Wait a minute, I made a mistake.
Oh?
It's more the same, isn't it?
No, I don't know. I don't know.
You like her, don't you?
This one's even more the same.
Who are you asking?
Oh, no, I made a mistake.
But I don't care.
What's this?
It looks like a bird's footprint.
Bird tracks?
Hmm?
This is the pattern. The pattern where the top is too big and the bottom is too narrow.
Shinji-aruaru.
Okay!
It looks really good.
It looks good!
Oh!
I am Mitsuhisa Shinju in the year 2023!
What's this all about, anyway? Shall I ask you this?
The Slam Dunk movie has just been released.
But the world is truly all about Slam Dunk, isn't it?
You're talking like it's Christmas.
As I thought, Shinju Mitsuhisa was shining so brightly.
I was under the impression that I wanted to do it to Mitsuhisa Shinju, too.
That's a roundabout way of giving up.
I'm a guy.
Is this right? To begin with.
It's not right. Wait a minute.
What? Was it like this?
Oh, no, no, no.
Is Motoki like this?
Wait a minute.
Did you see the diagonal?
Yes, I think so.
Did you see any diagonal bars?
Oh, no.
I'm just going to let him get mad at me.
LOL!
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna be pissed.
I'm a bad quitter.
I didn't give up until the end, and now I'm here.
Oh, you're using two cards.
Okay, I'll go.
I'll be right back.
GOGO.
Oh, you did it?
Not at all.
I don't think that's it.
What's this?
What is it?
Laughs.
Hey, hey, it's not from your profile, is it?
No?
Not exactly.
Like a rabbit.
What's that?
I don't think so.
Rabbit.
I fall asleep on the way to the rabbit.
Good luck.
Turtle, aren't you a turtle?
It's a tortoise, isn't it?
Oh, just right.
Oh, no.
You look a little drowsy.
Corrective powers.
Oh, that's cute.
Oh, he's cute.
Okay, okay.
Yes, it's done.
Okay, Hikari, your work is done.
Please announce it.
The year 2023...
I'll do my best to be a good bunny!
Pow!
By the way, this is...
This is called, um, the Three Families Grand Festival.
So, I have done what I have been asked to do
As a rabbit angel magical girl
I hope to do my best as a Usagi.
I think this will probably be displayed somewhere
so please come and take a look. Please come and see it.
Finally, can you two say a few words to the people watching this video?
Yes!
Pearl, please.
Yes! Well, I look forward to working with you all in 2023!
Dopyoon!
Dooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Well, super kotoyoro to you in 2023 too!
When I say super kotoyoro, I mean from the beginning to the end of this year.
When I say "Super koto yoroyo", please give me your best wishes from the beginning to the end of this year.
The first day of the new year is the first day of the new year, and Eavins' first sale opens tomorrow at 7:30 a.m. On the 2nd, we will have our first dream live performance, starting from welcoming you!
Let's welcome them together!Let's welcome you together!
We look forward to working with you in 2023!
We look forward to your first sale!
We look forward to seeing you soon!